{
    "subject": "resource/Chico_Hamilton_Trio",
    "predicate": "property/name",
    "object": "Chico Hamilton Trio",
    "human_readable": "The name of Chico Hamilton Trio is Chico Hamilton Trio.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9627865552902222,
            "question": "Who are Chico Hamilton Trio?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9579062461853027,
            "question": "Is Chico Hamilton Trio a band?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9435287117958069,
            "question": "Who or what is Chico Hamilton Trio?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7790268659591675,
            "question": "How would you describe Chico Hamilton Trio?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48891350626945496,
            "question": "What is the name of this famous musical trio?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18427884578704834,
            "question": "Can you tell me the name of this musical group?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18297043442726135,
            "question": "What is the full name of this music group?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18246479332447052,
            "question": "What is the name of the musical group?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1451428234577179,
            "question": "What is the collective name given to this group of musicians?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.11191786080598831,
            "question": "Give me the name of this jazz ensemble."
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The name of Chico Hamilton Trio is Chico Hamilton Trio.",
            "html": "dbpedia_879_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the collective name given to this group of musicians?",
            "html": "dbpedia_879_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the musical group?",
            "html": "dbpedia_879_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the full name of this music group?",
            "html": "dbpedia_879_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_879_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_879_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_879_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_879_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_879_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_879_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_879_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_879_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_879_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_879_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nThe provided text explicitly states \"The Chico Hamilton Trio\" multiple times as the name of the album and musical group. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe query asks to verify if the name of \"Chico Hamilton Trio\" is indeed \"Chico Hamilton Trio,\" which is directly supported by the repeated mentions in the provided context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}